urb.com 2013-05-18

# Legal | Privacy Policy | Terms Of Service | URB | URB Magazine :: Music | Style | Culture

URB Magazine and its parent company (NativeSon Media, Inc.) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of www.urb.com. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users’ right to privacy and because we value our relationships with our users.

NativeSon Media collects information about users during their registration for certain sections of our Website. When users request pages from our Web server, the server automatically attempts to identify the user’s domain name, but not the e-mail address. We also track certain information, in the aggregate, on pages and features that users access or view.

Users electing to subscribe to newsletters or magazines, enter contests or to access special sections, are required to supply certain personal information during a “registration” process. Information collected through these forms may be used by NativeSon Media, Inc. to gather broad demographic information about our users in general, for audits, and to perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our Website.

NativeSon Media, Inc. may periodically send out e-mail newsletters to our users about products, services, events or other news using e-mail addresses provided at registration or otherwise. Upon request, NativeSon Media, Inc. will remove users (and their information) from our database or permit them to “opt-out” of any further e-mail newsletter lists. If you receive any such e-mail messages that you do not wish to receive again in the future, simply click on the ‘Unsubscribe’ link contained in the footer of the email message.

If you provide us with any personal information, such as address, e-mail, telephone and fax numbers, as well as demographic and customer identification, we will not disclose (share, sell or divulge) it to third parties unless we have informed you, been authorized by you, or are required to do so by law. NativeSon Media will maintain this information in accordance with our strict security and confidentiality standards. To change or update your personal information please send a “remove” email (as explained above) and re-register with the new information.

This Website contains links to other Websites. NativeSon Media, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.

NativeSon Media, Inc. uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Nonetheless, NativeSon Media, Inc. does not guarantee the security, accuracy or completeness of any such information or procedures.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this Website, you may write to us at the following postal address:

NativeSon Media, Inc.  
Attention: Website Privacy Questions  
8484 Wilshire Blvd.  
Ste 560  
Los Angeles, CA 90211
